Optimus Prime UP059
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Optimus Prime
1998 -- 2006
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
School of Arts and Sciences
UP059
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains issues of Optimus Prime first published in November, 1998. It is a student literary magazine devoted to poetry and line drawings. It is published irregularly.
- Optimus Prime, 1998 -- 2006; UP059.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains issues of Optimus Prime first published in November, 1998. It is a student literary magazine devoted to poetry and line drawings. It is published irregularly.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Optimus Prime, 1998 -- 1999; UP059.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Volume
    1
  - Optimus Prime, 1999 -- 2000; UP059.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    2
  - Optimus Prime, 2000-01-01; UP059.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    3
  - Optimus Prime, 2002; UP059.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    Volume, issue
    4, 2
  - Optimus Prime, 2002; UP059.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    4, 3
  - Optimus Prime, 2002-10; UP059.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    5, 1
  - Optimus Prime, 2003; UP059.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    Summer
    5, 3
  - Optimus Prime, 2003-10; UP059.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Optimus Prime, Winter, 2003; UP059.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Optimus Prime, Fall, 2004; UP059.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Optimus Prime, Winter, 2005; UP059.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    Winter edition.
  - Optimus Prime, Spring, 2005; UP059.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    Spring edition.
  - Optimus Prime, Fall, 2005; UP059.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    Fall edition.
  - Optimus Prime, Winter, 2005; UP059.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Optimus Prime, Spring, 2006; UP059.001.001.00015 (Box 1)